Hi, Michael. Hi, Danny.
你好,Michael.你好,Danny.
Hi, Nancy.
你好,Nancy.
Yvonne, have you met our new tenants?
Yvonne,见过我们的新房客了吗?
Not yet.
还没有.
Yvonne Washington, Michael Chung and Danny DeMarco.
Yvonne Washington, Michael Chung和Danny DeMarco.
They moved in last weekend.
他们是上周末搬进来的.
It was last weekend, right?
是上周末,对吗?
Just last Saturday.
就在上周六.
Of course. How could I forget that sofa?
当然.我怎么可能忘记那张沙发呢?
How did you finally get it into the apartment?
最后你们是怎么把它弄进房间的?
Very slowly and very carefully.
慢慢地,非常小心地搬进去的.
Yvonne, do you live here, too?
Yvonne,你也住这儿吗?
No, no. Nancy and I are business partners,
不,不.Nancy和我是生意伙伴,
so I'm here quite a bit.
所以我经常来这.
Oh. What kind of business?
Oh. 你们做哪一行?
Interior design.
室内装潢设计.
Do you need help with your new place?
你们的新地方需要装修吗?
With our furniture? Impossible!
就我们这些家具?不可能!
Oh, I hardly think so.
Oh,我不这么认为.
You haven't seen the sofa.
你没见过我们的沙发.
Besides, I'm sure Lisa will help us redecorate.
而且,我相信Lisa会帮我们重新装饰的.
-Lisa?   -Lisa's my girlfriend.
-Lisa?   -Lisa是我的女朋友.
Just getting home from work, Danny?
刚下班回家吗,Danny?
Yeah. I'm beat.
是的.我累死了.
Where do you work?
你在哪里工作?
Kinko's. The night shift.
在Kinko复印社.夜班.
You too, Michael?
你也是吗,Michael?
Oh no. Michael is a serious film maker.
Oh不是.Michael可是位严肃的电影制片人.
-Danny...   -Really?
-Danny...   -真的吗?
I'm a graduate student in Film Studies.
我是研究生,电影研究专业.
And I do work at night, occasionally.
有时晚上我也打些工.
Actually, Yvonne, we've got to run.
真的,Yvonne,我们得走了.
Everything OK in the apartment?
公寓的情况都好吗?
So far, so good.
到目前为止还行.
Good. We'll see you later.
好.那再见了.
-Nice to meet you.  -Bye.
-很高兴认识你们.    -再见.
It must be hard to work all night.
整夜工作一定很累.
Unless you sleep all day.
除非你白天睡一整天.